edwardwadsworth.com 2001-12-01

# Edward Wadsworth for Hair Privacy Policy

### PRIVACY POLICY

**[USA ONLY]** ****

The policies below are applicable to www.edwardswadsworth.com produced and maintained by Edward Wadsworth For Hair. Edward Wadsworth For Hair is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of consumers of its products and services.  Throughout cyberspace, we want to contribute to providing a safe and secure environment for consumers. If you don't find your concern addressed here, feel free to contact us by e-mail or phone **503-292-8287** ****

**_What Personal Information Do We Collect?_ ****__**

One of the basic principles we've followed in designing this Web site is that we ask for only the information we need to provide the service you've requested. As a result, the answer to this question depends almost entirely on how you choose to make use of our Web site and our growing list of Web site services. 

Edward Wadsworth For Hair collects personal information only during (i) online shopping (ii) when client questionnaires are filled out (iii) when questions are submitted on the answer page.  Edward Wadsworth For Hair may use such information to fulfill purchase orders, track compliance with the site's rules and regulations or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when users provide the information). In the event Edward Wadsworth For Hair **** plans to publicly post any such information on a site, [users are provided prior notification of such posting and given the option of preventing such posting and only the user's first name is used.] Specifically requesting it from you collects personal information.  Generally this occurs when you register at a site, request a service, or purchase products.

In addition to the use of personal information to operate Edward Wadsworth For Hair sites, an Edward Wadsworth For Hair site may also gather anonymous information, which may be used by Edward Wadsworth For Hair [or shared with third parties.] **** This collective data helps us determine how our customers use parts of the site, so we can improve our site and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many of you as possible. We also may provide statistical "ratings" information, but never information about you personally, to our Edward Wadsworth For Hair partners about how our members, collectively, use Edward Wadsworth For Hair. We do this so they too can understand how people use their areas of our site in order for them to provide you with the best possible experience as well.  This information is also used to generate advertising rates.  Generally this information is collected through "traffic data" and may entail the use of "Cookies" "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer.

**_Information We Ask About You_ **____

Sometimes, we may specifically ask for information about you when you sign up to use a service or when you order a product. We will need certain information -- such as name, Internet address or screen name, billing address, type of computer, credit card number -- in order to provide that service or product to you. We may also use that information to let you know of additional products and services about which you might be interested.  [You can choose not to receive such information if you don't want to by letting us know on the registration screen when you sign up for the product or service.]  We also may ask you for information about your interests so that both you and we can take advantage of the interactivity of the Internet, but you may always choose whether to respond or not. 

**_Use of Cookies_ ****__**

_What about "Cookies"?_ __

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. "Cookies" make Web-surfing easier for you by saving your passwords, purchases, and preferences while you're at our site.  The use of "Cookies" is standard in the Internet industry, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. By showing how and when guests use the site, "Cookies" help us see which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed.  This information is most easily tracked with "Cookies." "Cookies" in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept "Cookies."  If you prefer, you can set yours to refuse "Cookies" or to alert you when "Cookies" are being sent.  However, it is possible that some areas of the site, such as the shopping, contest, and game areas, will not function properly if you do so.

**_[How We Do Not Use Cookies_ ****__**

Our site never uses "Cookies" to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a cookie. Except as described above, we do not use information transferred through "Cookies" for any promotional or marketing purposes, nor is that information shared with any third parties whatsoever.  We do not use Cookies" to identify specific individuals, except in such cases as online shopping and contest registration (where a "Cookie" allows you to enter a contest every day without registering again each time).  You may occasionally get "Cookies" from our advertisers.  We do not control these "Cookies," and these "Cookies" are not subject to our "Cookie" policy.  The use of advertising "Cookies" sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. ********

**_How We Use the Information_ ****__**

We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our site or information that you may give us, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number, to any outside companies.  We may, however, share with our Web site partners aggregated statistical "ratings" information about the use of our site.  [Edward Wadsworth For Hair sites also use personal information to allow other companies to contact you regarding products and services that may be of interest to you (Secondary Uses). If an Edward Wadsworth For Hair site proposes to use personal information for Secondary Uses, you will be provided an opportunity to instruct the Edward Wadsworth For Hair site not to allow such contact.]  Edward Wadsworth For Hair does not sell any customer lists or e-mail addresses. However, we may partner with businesses to provide special services to our customers.  This type of use of personal information is called a Secondary Use because it is not necessary to the operation of the business or site.  For example, a site may offer discount coupons for services or related products. In many cases these discounts would be an added benefit to you. If an Edward Wadsworth For Hair site proposes to make a Secondary Use of your personal information you will be given an opportunity to instruct the Edward Wadsworth For Hair site not to allow such contact. You may contact us at any time in order to direct us to remove your information from future mailings.

Edward Wadsworth For Hair may also disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on Edward Wadsworth For Hair or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Edward Wadsworth For Hair, the site or the users of Edward Wadsworth For Hair, and (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Edward Wadsworth For Hair, the site or the public.

**_Links to Other Sites_ ****__**

Users should be aware that when you are on Edward Wadsworth For Hair sites you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control.  There are links on our site that take you to other Web sites outside our service.  For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" takes you off the Edward Wadsworth For Hair site. These links include links from advertisers, sponsors and partners that may use Edward Wadsworth For Hair's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.  Always be aware of where you end up. Please keep in mind that whenever you give out personal information online - for example, via message boards or chat - that information can be collected and used by people you don't know. While Edward Wadsworth For Hair strives to protect your personal information and privacy, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk.  Finally, please note that this policy applies only to Edward Wadsworth For Hair and Web sites that carry the Edward Wadsworth For Hair brand, and not to other companies' or organizations' Web sites to which we link. We have clearly marked Edward Wadsworth For Hair and these branded Web sites with our logo so you know where this policy applies.

**_Security Policy_ **____

The importance of security for all personal information associated with you is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Personal information collected by Edward Wadsworth For Hair sites is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. In many instances, such as in the case of credit card numbers, the personal information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction.  Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access, each having signed confidentiality agreements. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution. 

**_Chat Sessions and Newsgroups_ ****__**

In addition to directly providing information to an Edward Wadsworth For Hair site, you might also provide personal information through chat sessions, e-mail exchanges or newsgroups made available to you on Edward Wadsworth For Hair. The Privacy Policy does not cover this type of transfer of your personal information. You should always be careful when distributing your personal information in this manner. And remember that online chat sessions and newsgroup use is considered public and you are responsible for your actions in these areas.

**_Your Acceptance of These Terms_ **____

By using this site, you signify your acceptance of the Edward Wadsworth For Hair Privacy Policy.  If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our sites.  Your continued use of the Edward Wadsworth For Hair sites and our affiliate sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. 

**_Changes_** **__**

Edward Wadsworth For Hair is committed to maintaining its position as a premier site on the Internet. As our site continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our website. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately.

**_Questions_ ****__**

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the Don Dutro edwardwadsworth.com 8650 SW Canyon Rd. Portland, OR  97225 or send an email to the [President] at ddutro@edwardwadsworth.com. 

To return to the Web site, please use the "Back" button on your browser or Click Here to go to our Products Page.
